Feinstein International Center Records UA197
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2015 accessions, 2013 -- 2015; UA197.003.000002; 41 Digital Object(s)
  - "It's Better to Sweat than to Die:" Rural-to-Urban Migration, Northern Karamoja, Uganda, 2014; UA197.003.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 31.32 Megabytes
    "It's Better to Sweat than to Die:" Rural-to-Urban Migration, Northern Karamoja, Uganda, by Elizabeth Stites, John Burns, and Darlington Akabwai
  - Looking back to look ahead? Reviewing key lessons from Operation Lifeline Sudan and past humanitarian operations in South Sudan, 2014; UA197.003.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); .38 Megabytes
    Looking back to look ahead? Reviewing key lessons from Operation Lifeline Sudan and past humanitarian operations in South Sudan. Working Paper 24, by Daniel Maxwell, Martina Santschi, and Rachel Gordon
  - Against the Grain: The Cereal Trade in Darfur, 2014; UA197.003.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.45 Megabytes
    Against the Grain: The Cereal Trade in Darfur, by Margie Buchanan-Smith et al
  - The war-wounded and recovery in Northern Uganda, 2014; UA197.003.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); .3 Megabytes
    The war-wounded and recovery in Northern Uganda. Briefing Paper 6, by Dyan Mazurana and Teddy Atim
  - Participatory Impact Assessment: A Design Guide, 2014; UA197.003.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.56 Megabytes
    Participatory Impact Assessment: A Design Guide, by Andy Catley et al
  - Surveying livelihoods, service delivery and governance: baseline evidence from South Sudan, 2014; UA197.003.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.5 Megabytes
    Surveying livelihoods, service delivery and governance: baseline evidence from South Sudan. Working Paper 21, by Marco d'Errico, Karolina Kozlowska, and Daniel Maxwell
  - Lessons Learned from the Somalia Famine and the Greater Horn of Africa Crisis 2011-2012: Desk Review of Literature, 2014; UA197.003.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.49 Megabytes
    Lessons Learned from the Somalia Famine and the Greater Horn of Africa Crisis 2011-2012: Desk Review of Literature, by Daniel Maxwell et al
  - Making Gender-Just Remedy and Reparations Possible: Upholding the Rights of Women and Girls in Uganda's Greater North, 2014; UA197.003.00034; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.06 Megabytes
    Making Gender-Just Remedy and Reparations Possible: Upholding the Rights of Women and Girls in Uganda's Greater North. Briefing Paper, by Dyan Mazurana and Teddy Atim
  - Surveying livelihoods, service delivery and governance: baseline evidence from Uganda, 2014; UA197.003.00035; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.42 Megabytes
    Surveying livelihoods, service delivery and governance: baseline evidence from Uganda. Working Paper 12, by Dyan Mazurana et al
  - Inhumanity and Humanitarian Action: Protection Failures in Sri Lanka, 2014; UA197.003.00036; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.32 Megabytes
    Inhumanity and Humanitarian Action: Protection Failures in Sri Lanka, by Norah Niland
  - Breaking the Hourglass: Partnerships in Remote Management Settings, The Cases of Syria and Iraqi Kurdistan, 2015; UA197.003.00037; 1 Digital Object(s); .27 Megabytes
    Breaking the Hourglass: Partnerships in Remote Management Settings, The Cases of Syria and Iraqi Kurdistan. Briefing Paper 1, by Kimberly Howe, Elizabeth Stites, and Danya Chudacoff
  - Another Humanitarian Crisis in Somalia? Learning from the 2011 Famine, 2014; UA197.003.00038; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.51 Megabytes
    Another Humanitarian Crisis in Somalia? Learning from the 2011 Famine, by Daniel Maxwell and Nisar Majid
  - Community-based Animal Health Workers in the Horn of Africa: An Evaluation for the US Office for Foreign Disaster Assistance, 2014; UA197.003.00039; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.3 Megabytes
    Community-based Animal Health Workers in the Horn of Africa: An Evaluation for the US Office for Foreign Disaster Assistance, by Tim Leyland et al
  - The impact of serious crimes during the war on households today in Northern Uganda, 2014; UA197.003.00040; 1 Digital Object(s); .29 Megabytes
    The impact of serious crimes during the war on households today in Northern Uganda. Briefing Paper 5, by Dyan Mazurana and Teddy Atim
  - Engaging Male Youth in Karamoja, Uganda: An examination of the factors driving the perpetration of violence and crime by young men in Karamoja and the applicability of a communications and relationships program to address related behavior, 2014; UA197.003.00041; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.63 Megabytes
    Engaging Male Youth in Karamoja, Uganda: An examination of the factors driving the perpetration of violence and crime by young men in Karamoja and the applicability of a communications and relationships program to address related behavior, by Elizabeth Stites et al
- 2020 accessions, circa 2008 -- 2017; UA197.000270; 19.7 Megabytes; 8 Digital Object(s)
  Transferred by Feinstein International Center, 2019, accession UA-2020-050.
  This series contains Feinstein International Center publications.
  - Participatory Impact Assessment: A Guide for Practitioners, circa 2008; UA197.000271; 2.72 Megabytes
  - Humanitarian Agenda 2015: Final Report, The State of the Humanitarian Enterprise, 2008 March; UA197.000272; 1.63 Megabytes
  - Stop the Sexual Assault Against Humanitarian and Development Aid Workers, 2017 May; UA197.000273; 1.03 Megabytes
  - Winning Hearts and Minds? Examining the Relationship Between Aid and Security in Afghanistan, 2012 January; UA197.000274; 2.16 Megabytes
  - Planning from the Future: Is the Humanitarian System Fit for Purpose?, 2016 November; UA197.000275; 6.79 Megabytes
  - Milk Matters: The Impact of Dry Season Livestock Support on Milk Supply and Child Nutrition in Somali Region, Ethiopia, 2012 May; UA197.000276; 1.84 Megabytes
  - Water, Livestock, and Malnutrition: Findings from an Impact Assessment of "Community Resilience to Acute Malnutrition" Programming in the Dar Sila Region of Eastern Chad, 2012–2015, 2016 December; UA197.000277; 1.52 Megabytes
  - Lifting Livelihoods with Livestock: A review of REST's livestock value addition practices in Raya Azebo, Ethiopia and potentials for diversification, 2011 November; UA197.000278; 2.03 Megabytes